美式语音节奏。所有文化都会使用手势；最近一位发展心理学家
The American speech music. All cultures gesture, and recently a developmental
威斯康星大学的发展生理学家 Ali Bali 博士提出，手势会
physiologist at University of Wisconsin, Dr. Ali Bali, put forth that gestures
因为我们的嘴和手在大脑中密切联系在一起。
accompany speech because our mouths and hands are closely linked in the brain. You
你也许注意过，婴儿会一边咿呀发声，一边按节奏挥动手。
may have noticed babies saying ga ga ga and moving their hands to the beat. It's
你不需要夸张地手舞足蹈，但重要的是把手势融入
not necessary for you to gesticulate wildly, but it is important to integrate
你的语音节奏和身体手势结合起来。为此，你会
the rhythm of your speech music with physical gestures. To this end, you'll be
敲桌子、打响指，甚至可以拉橡皮筋。
tapping the table, snapping your fingers, and maybe even stretching a rubber band.
“我的语言呢？”一位巴基斯坦数据库分析师说：“我以前没这样想过自己的语言。”
my language? A Pakistani database analyst said, I didn't think about my own language
她说，他们说话时也有语调，但不像美式英语那么明显。
in this way before. There is intonation when we speak, but not as much as in
比美式英语少。现在分析过之后，她发现自己的语言其实也有节奏，
American English. Now that I've analyzed it, I found my language to be rhythmic
很多地方，我们也会使用同样的升降语调。
too. In many places, we do the same up and down intonation. I must not have realized
因为我说话时并不会去想语言本身。
it because I speak without thinking about the language itself. It's really
比较两种语言风格，然后提取出某些相似点，真的很有意思。
interesting to compare both language styles and then to extract certain
我从来没有这样想过。
resemblances from them. I never thought of it in that way.